Today we will tell you
how you can update your email ID in your account through the iMobile application.
Friends, if the
iMobile application is not installed on your mobile yet, then
in the previous video we told you how to
activate the iMobile. Its link is
given in the description box. You
can activate the iMobile from there. Now we will login here by
printing the iMobile application in four colors.
See, our application has been logged in here.
After logging in, you will
see that at the bottom corner, you have to click on the
service column
and select the internet. On the next page,
you will see the option of Insta Banking Service. By
clicking on it, you will get the option to update the
email ID at the very last second number.
You have to
update your email ID here. On this page, you
will see that on the second line, you will get the option to enter your email ID.
Here,
print your email ID and click on the submit button. On the
next page, you will see that it is
asking for authorization of your ATM card.
Friends,
some playlist numbers are given in the form ABCD on the back of your ATM card.
You have to see the back of your card.  Seeing this, the one
who is asking for BCD number here should be
entered, so like
I have entered the CR code here
and clicked on the submit button,
now see your email ID has been successfully
updated in your account and
we have also received its confirmation message, so this
was the process of updating your email ID,
friends, if you liked this video then
like this video and subscribe to this channel.